Casey Hunt

Creative Technologies and Design Master's Student University of Colorado Boulder, ATLAS Institute <u>casey.hunt@colorado.edu</u> <u>casey-l-hunt.medium.com</u>

Casey Hunt is a multidisciplinary and collaborative researcher interested in the intersection of critical design, ubiquitous sensing, and civic technology. She prides herself on her diverse skill set and believes that diversity (in teams and in knowledge) is invaluable. From nationally recognized leadership development training, to design theory, to the scientific method, to full-stack development, Casey is constantly pushing the boundaries of cross-domain exploration. It is this broad-but-focused view that positions her to undertake innovative projects like her work on an award winning browser extension to encourage good digital hygiene in children and her ongoing research on soft-thermocouples.

Education

2019 - 2021 (Expected) University of Colorado Boulder, ATLAS Institute

M.S., Creative Technologies and Design

2011 - 2015 University of Utah

B.S., Biological Chemistry

Research Experience

Jun 2020 - Present University of Colorado Boulder, ATLAS Institute

THING Lab

Associated Researcher

Teaching Experience

May 2020 - Present CU Science Discovery

Instructor/Curriculum Development

Course: Digital Art and Media - Web based digital art techniques for at-risk high

school students

Course: Engineering in the Maker Age - Design theory and making techniques

for high school students

Course: Minecraft Adventures - Drag and drop mod development for late

elementary/early middle school students.

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020 Hackaday.io

Instructor

Course: Art + Code - P5.js course reviewing the basics of art theory and

composition through the lens of procedurally generated art.

Jan 2020 - May 2020 University of Colorado Boulder, ATLAS Institute

Associate Lecturer

Course: Process - An introduction to design theory, Adobe Creative Cloud, and

the graphic design process for non-majors

Professional Experience

2019 - Present Apsis Healthcare

Lead Principal User Experience Designer and Developer

Building wireframes and conducting UX research for biotech manufacturing software solutions. Works in close collaboration with the development team to create user interfaces that support back-end plans and challenges while using

user interviews to fit the software to enterprise client specifications.

2019 - 2020 **Zavvie**

User Experience Designer

Primary designer collaborating with the web development team to create new user-friendly products for real estate enterprise clients. Worked directly with the CEO, CTO, and CMO to develop new brand identity and marketing materials.

2017 - 2019 **NextCure**

System Administrator and Quality System Associate

Managed Manufacturing Execution System (MES) maintenance, testing, and

expansion for a team of 20 pharmaceutical scientists, engineers, and

immunologists. Observed manufacturing personnel to ensure FDA compliance,

and created institutional procedures to support accurate and safe manufacturing of pharmaceutical products.

2015 - 2017 **Consolidated Electrical Distributors**

Credit Analyst and Database Administrator

Assisted in the development, adoption, and implementation of a custom built, company-wide customer database. Maintained the local chapter of the customer database, and reported outages and bugs to the national development team. At the same time, building and maintaining customer relationships with contractors across the region to ensure they delivered accurate and timely payment, without alienating them or their business.

2015 Capstone Laboratories

Quality Control Chemist

Testing incoming raw materials and outgoing finished products to ensure FDA compliance. Primarily focused on FTIR and wet chemistry techniques. Some HPLC experience. Managed a large portion of the lab's experimental data and created user-flows in the Access database for any incoming testing equipment.

Leadership Experience

CU Boulder ATLAS Institute Aug 2020 - Present

Graduate Program Assistant

Communicating professional and institutional opportunities to the graduate students of the ATLAS Institute. This role requires building and sustaining a wide array of relationships across the university community, and leveraging those connections for the success of fellow graduate students. Conducts research on internal departmental communication strategies to maximize information dispersal while minimizing student overwhelm during the COVID-19 pandemic.

2015 - 2020 Kith Colorado

Board of Directors

President of the Board 2017 to 2019

Managed social media, created and managed web presence, and assisted with the development and promotion of public programs. As president, lead a diverse and skilled team of public health experts, assisted in graduate student mentorship, and consulted on community ethnographic research.

Jun 2020 - Present

ATLAS Social Committee

Founding Member

While there are already many opportunities for connection in the CU ATLAS Institute, the social committee was formed as a grassroots effort to create social connection among graduate students. The committee is focused on creating programs that foster the development of friendships among students who are physically separated. Our programs have included collaborative art nights and online gameplay and have high engagement among both first year and returning students.

Research

Ongoing

Exploring Web Monetization for Nonprofit Organizations using Interledger Protocol

Mozilla Foundation Grant for the Web

Main Objectives: Explore novel ways for distributed funding models with a specific focus on data collection practices.

In Collaboration With: Aarjav Chauhan and Boulder Food Rescue

Race Bias in Landmark Based Face Recognition

Main Objectives: Expand existing research into the ways that racial bias enters facial recognition algorithms. In Collaboration with: Jed Brubaker, Morgan Scheuerman, Katy Weathington, Aarjav Chauhan, Emma Petersen, Liza Tolkin, Frank Stinar, Ketan Ramesh

Soft Thermocouple: Maximizing Accuracy of a Wearable Temperature Sensor

Main Objectives: Create a novel way to sense the state of a user with an accurate, wearable temperature sensor.

Past

Dancing Alone: Forging Community Bonds with Dance

Future Bound Speaker Series 2019

Main Objectives: Investigate the history of dance in community building and propose solutions that community leaders can implement in their own practices.

In Collaboration With: Meeshi Anjali, GroovaRoo Dance

Awards

2020	T9 Hacks Best Educational Software
2020	ATLAS Mask Design Challenge 1st Place Winner
2015	Employee of the Month University of Utah Housing
2014	NRHH Of-The Month Campus Winner - Passive Program
2014	NRHH Of-The Month Nominee - Residential Community
2014	NRHH Of-The Month Nominee - Resident Advisor
2014	NRHH Of-The Month Campus Winner - Passive Program

Certifications

2019 I	eading Change	Institute: Asheville	Training
--------	---------------	----------------------	----------

2015 American Chemical Society Certified

Technical Skills

Visual Basic, SQL, Python, JavaScript, P5.JS, Node.JS, Socket.io, HTML, CSS, C++, C#, Arduino, Unity, Figma, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Premiere Pro, Adobe Illustrator, Adobe InDesign, Procreate